

Taylor Wright

Full Stack Web Developer

With a 14-year history of high-level customer service in a fast paced, creative environment, I have built a career focused on sales, retention, and resolutions. Looking to broaden my career scope and bring my strong dedication, responsibility, and motivation while utilizing my Full Stack Web Development qualifications obtained through the University of Denver.

Professional Skills

Customer Service
Web Development
HTML
Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)
JavaScript
Node.js
MySQL
MongoDB
Web Development
Sales
Data Entry
Data Analysis
Electronic Medical Record (EMR)

How to reach me:

Phone: (719) 453-8516 Email: tjwri25@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/taylo

r-wright-56a671184/

Website:

https://tjwri25.github.io/portfolio/

Educational Training

University of Denver Full Stack Web Development

• 2020-2021

Toni & Guy Hairdressing Academy-Colorado Springs

• 2006-2007

Ponderosa High School High School Diploma

• 2002-2006

Work Experience

En Gedi Salon – Independent Hairstylist

Nov 2013 - Present

Here I am able to express my creative side while still being able to manage my own business. With a high level of customer service, I can seek out new clients and retain more. Managing the scheduling, inventory and finances from beginning to end.

Floyd's 99 Barbershop -Hairstylist Aug 2009 - Present

Fast paced environment with a lot of clients, but even then, I was able to build a relationship with them with the short time I was with them. Able to understand their wants in their look, providing options for products from our wide inventory and delivering top level styling and customer service.

Work Experience Cont'd

Just Associates, Inc. - Patient Identity Expert Aug 2016- June 2019

I had to have a high level of attention to detail for Medical Records clean up. With that attention to detail, we are using multiple external data bases and systems in a virtual setting. Client systems include: EPIC, Nextgate, All Scripts, Soarian, Meditech and Cerner. These systems were used to determine patient's eligibility to be merged. In my time with Just Associates, I have been chosen for increasingly difficult projects due to my high level of accuracy and timely manner of completion.

Great Clips Inc. – Assistant Manager

Apr 2008 - Aug 2009

Managing the day-to-day workings of the store from scheduling, working and customer escalations. Working with employees to improve their abilities, providing feedback real time and giving achievable goals.